Get off the bench and get into the game.
The Benchwarmers is a comedy film directed by Dennis Dugan.
A trio of guys try and make up for missed opportunities in childhood by forming a
three-player baseball team to compete against standard little league squads.
Gus, played by Rob Schneider.
Richie, played by David Spade.
Clark, played by Jon Heder.
Liz, played by Molly Sims.
Mel, played by Jon Lovitz.
Carlos, played by Amaury Nolasco.
The Benchwarmers is a 2006 American sports-comedy film directed by Dennis Dugan, written by
Allen Covert and Nick Swardson, and produced by Adam Sandler and Jack Giarraputo.
The film stars Rob Schneider, David Spade, Jon Heder, Jon Lovitz, Craig Kilborn, Molly Sims, and Tim Meadows, with Swardson, Erinn Bartlett,
Amaury Nolasco, Bill Romanowski, Sean Salisbury, Matt Weinberg, John Farley, Reggie Jackson, and Joe Gnoffo in supporting roles.
It tells the story of three nerds and a billionaire forming a
titular baseball team to take on Little League teams.
Produced by Sandler's production company Happy Madison Productions in association with Revolution Studios,
The Benchwarmers was released in the United States on April 7, 2006, by Columbia Pictures.
The film was met with negative reviews.
A direct-to-video sequel titled Benchwarmers 2:
Breaking Balls  was released in January 2019.
The film explores themes of sports, baseball, pizza, paperboy, homerun.
The tone is lighthearted.